The heart will store energy in a fascial environment,
心臓は、顔面環境にエネルギーを蓄え、
where it will support the heart's electricity in its ascent and descent.
心臓の電気を上昇と下降の両方でサポートします。
There's like an imprint of an ease.
そこには、容易さの痕跡のようなものがあります。
Some people are in a systolic function or more in a diastolic function.
収縮期機能にある人もいれば、拡張期機能にある人もいます。
Normally, there should be a balance.
通常、ほぼ均衡が保たれているはずです。
In a way, it will repeat its embryonic movement quite directly in its motion.
ある意味で、それはその動きの中で、かなり直接的にその胚性運動を繰り返します。
You will feel a movement more like this, or more like this.
あなたは、むしろこのように、あるいはむしろこのように、動きを感じるでしょう。
For example, people who...
例えば、ある人々は...
are too much in a systolic movement, these are people who seek
収縮期の動きに偏りすぎている人は、何かを求めています。
and who at the same time
そして同時に、
can go into exhaustion. Or conversely, these are people who start here and are
疲弊してしまうこともあります。あるいは逆に、ここから出発して、常に
always looking for that support point at the bottom, that's diastole. Remember,
下にあるこの支点を求めている人々、それが拡張期です。覚えていますか？
the heart does this kind of looping, where the ventricular system that
心臓はこの種のループを描き、心室系は
was above
上部にあったものが、
becomes below with a significant support point in the space between the atria
心房間の空間に重要な支点を持って下部になります。
and the...
そして...
When the heart performs a systole, it will ascend, a supination movement,
心臓が収縮期になると、上昇し、回外運動を行い、
it will tend to verticalize and it performs a detorsion.
垂直になろうとし、ねじれを解消します。
This is where there is a movement of the aorta opening, why?
そこでは大動脈の動きが開きますが、なぜでしょうか？
To receive all the blood, so there's a kind of congestion that will
すべての血液を受け入れるため、ここに一種のうっ血が
happen here.
生じます。
And when it descends, all the blood from the aorta goes into the system.
そして下降するとき、大動脈のすべての血液が全身に送られます。
That's why sometimes some people confuse systolic movements.
だから、収縮期の動きを
with the downward movement.
下降の動きと混同する人がいるのです。
You see that systole,
収縮期は、
is the moment it ejects.
血液を駆出する瞬間です。
And that's why when it comes back down,
そして、下降するときに、
it refills.
再び満たされます。
I do this,
私はこれを行います。
so I eject the volume,
つまり、血液量を駆出しますが、
but I increase my pressure
圧力を高めます。
in my aortic arch system.
大動脈弓のシステム内で。
However, when I descend,
しかし、下降するときは、
I fill,
満たされますが、
but I eject the aorta.
大動脈を駆出します。
Do you have the impression
心臓が垂直になろうとする傾向があるか、
that the heart tends to verticalize
それとも水平になろうとする傾向があるか、
or to horizontalize?
という印象を受けますか？
Because the heart, it verticalizes and goes up, or if it horizontalizes
なぜなら、心臓は垂直になって上昇するか、あるいは水平になって
and goes down.
下降するからです。
And so, we're going to take three points of support.
では、3つの支持点を取りましょう。
A point of support that will be at the level of the aortic space, which is the second intercostal space
1つの支持点は大動脈スペース、つまり第2肋間スペースにあります。
here,
ここです。
and a pulmonary space, and the hypothenar
そして肺スペース、そして小指球筋が
eminence will be placed on the apex of the heart, like this.
心臓の先端にこのように置かれます。
The heart will react according to two large systems
心臓は、それに非常に近い2つの大きなシステムに反応します。
that are very close to it.
それは、
One, according to the liver.
1つは肝臓の機能に応じて。
Two, according to the stomach.
2つは胃の機能に応じて。
Three, according to the lungs.
3つは肺の機能に応じて。
And four, according to the kidneys.
そして4つは腎臓の機能に応じて。
It will always try in its environment to help the
心臓は常にその環境において、最大限に
maximum the lungs, the liver, the stomach and
肺、肝臓、胃、そして
the kidneys. It will always try to maintain
腎臓を助けようとします。心臓は常にこの圧力を維持しようとします。
this pressure because it is a volume regulator. We must consider
なぜなら、心臓は体積の調整器だからです。心臓は
the heart as
大動脈から下まで続く
a large artery with the aorta all the way down. So really consider
大きな動脈と考えるべきです。ですから、これを本当に
it as the octopus.
タコのように考えてください。
Systole, supination, in relation here.
収縮期、回外、ここに関して。
It will be a pronation movement.
これは回内運動になります。
So we have this, like this.
ですから、このように。
We'll see its environment, how it's placed.
その環境がどのように配置されているかを見てみましょう。
And then we'll place our hands on the liver.
そして、肝臓のレベルに手を置きます。
And we'll see how it reacts.
そして、それがどのように反応するかを見てみましょう。
On a fascial plane.
顔面平面上で。
The aorta, if you look closely anatomically, it actually goes quite far back, like that.
大動脈は、解剖学的に注意深く見ると、実際にはかなり後ろからこのように出ています。
So it's difficult to see it.
ですから、それを見るのは難しいです。
We just know that it is with a common fascial environment, with the
私たちは、それが気管支や食道と共通の筋膜環境にあることだけを知っています。
bronchi and the esophagus.
気管支と食道。
which inserts at the level of this vertebra which is very frequently in adaptation. That's called the rhythmic zone. This is a neurosensory zone, this is the rhythmic zone, this is the metabolic zone, this is the urogenital zone. The heart, to have a good movement, must have a good relationship with the diaphragm.
それは、非常に頻繁に適応しているこの椎骨のレベルに挿入されます。
So, there is a direct relationship via this fascial continuity of the arch and the aorta.
さて、大動脈弓と大動脈の筋膜の連続性を介した直接的な関係があります。
Remember the passage of the aorta,
大動脈の通路を思い出してください。
it's the zone, it's the zone, it's the zone, it's the zone.
それはゾーン、それはゾーン、それはゾーン、それはゾーンです。
deep where it really comes from both sides of the diaphragmatic pillars.
横隔膜の脚が両側から本当に来る深い場所です。
To work a
作業するために
heart, the diaphragm must absolutely be open and flexible. Don't forget that there is another
心臓には、横隔膜が完全に開いていて柔軟でなければなりません。まだあることを忘れないでください。
important passage which is related to the esophagus. Yesterday we saw the embryonic fulcrum,
もう一つの重要な通路は食道に関するものです。昨日、私たちは胚性支点を見ました。
pre-pattern that was placed at the primitive line at the coccyx with the arrival point.
原線レベル、尾骨レベルに到達点を持つプレパターン。
Now what we're going to do is put our hand on the heart and let the hand
今からすることは、心臓に手を置き、手をそのままにしておくことです。
Follow the fascial movement.
顔の動きに従ってください。
The tissue, if you listen, will show you if the heart is more towards
組織は、あなたが耳を傾ければ、心臓が収縮期に向かっているのか、それとも拡張期に向かっているのかを示してくれるでしょう。
systole or towards diastole.
収縮期か拡張期か。
Is it because of my liver reacting?
それは私の肝臓が反応しているからですか？
Is it because of my stomach?
それは私の胃のせいですか？
Or is it because of my kidneys?
それとも私の腎臓のせいですか？
Three levels.
3つのレベル。
And then we'll see if it can rebalance from there.
そして、そこから再均衡できるかどうかを見てみましょう。
And the lungs too.
そして肺も。